I don't know if you know this about
y'all, but this is another thing I
learned during the pandemic. I don't
know if you know this about y'all, but
the average American takes three dry
wipes after they go number
two. Three dry wipes,
sir. If you take more than three dry
wipes, you should probably talk to
somebody.
If you take less than three dry wipes,
you probably super itchy right
now. I
was I was an average American. I took
three dry wipes. No
longer. I now take two dry wipes and one
moist
wipe. I now use flushable wipes.
I don't like it, but I can't stop doing
it. Fellas, you have no idea how much of
your self-esteem is tied into the health
of your booty
[Laughter]
hole. Ladies, if your man having
self-esteem issues, get him some moist
wipes. You can look at a man in the eyes
and tell when he has moist wipes swag.
It's a lifechanging situation.
What's your name, ma'am? Caroline.
Caroline. Caroline, I want you to look
at this dude right here. You see this
dude right here? See how he kind of got
like a black dude's lean going
on? Super cool. Don't care about
nothing. He don't even like that shirt,
but he put it on cuz he don't
care. It's a top-notch dude. See how he
leaning over, claiming his woman like a
primal man.
You see that? Legs wide open. You see
that? It's a top-notch booty hole on
that dude right
there. Top
notch A1 booty
hole. All right, Caroline.
Adversely, I want you to turn around.
You see this dude right
here in a red
hoodie. You see how you see how he
looking? Looking kind of timid like he
don't he don't really want to be
here. But he did something wrong to his
girl. So now he can't say no to her. So
now he
here. See how he wearing a hoodie and
some shorts. He confused. He didn't know
where he was
going. You see that? See how his legs
crossed?
He's got a questionable booty
[Applause]
hole. You
got He worried about
streets. You got to get you some moist.
It's not a bad thing. Just need you some
moist
[Music]
wipes. And I don't want to hear nothing
from the bedet people.
Okay. What you're doing is
wrong and
blasphemous and I don't support
[Music]
it. That is not something my Jesus was.
Okay. And you still got to dry off. Why
are
you You didn't You didn't skit. You
didn't How are you drying off? You
didn't even